Martha Graham Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Photographic Material (Box 239-273)
  - Clytemnestra
    - McDonald, McGehee, MG, Ross, other (Box-folder 259/12)
    - McDonald, McGehee, Ross (Box-folder 243/29, 259/13)
    - McDonald, MG, Ross (Box-folder 243/30)
    - McDonald, McGehee, MG, Ross, Taylor, Turney, Winter, Yuriko (Box-folder 259/11)
    - McDonald, MG, Ross, other [Graff] (Box-folder 243/31)
    - McDonald, MG, Turney, other (Box-folder 243/32)
    - [McDonald], MG, Ross, Turney (Box-folder 259/14)
    - McDonald, MG, Ross, Turney (Box-folder 243/33, 259/15)
    - McDonald, MG, Winter (Box-folder 243/34)
    - McDonald, MG, other (Box-folder 243/35)
    - McDonald, Winter; McDonald, Winter, other (Box-folder 243/36)
    - McGehee (Box-folder 259/16)
    - McGehee, others (Box-folder 259/19)
    - McGehee, MG, Ross (incl. negative) (Box-folder 259/17)
    - McGehee, MG, Ross, Taylor (Box-folder 259/18)
    - MG (Box-folder 259/20)
    - MG, Ross (incl. negative) (Box-folder 259/21)
    - MG, Ross (Box-folder 259/22)
    - MG, Ross, others (Box-folder 259/23)
    - MG, Taylor (Box-folder 259/24)
    - MG, Wood (Box-folder 259/25)
    - MG, Yuriko, others (Box-folder 259/26)
    - MG, spear bearers (Box-folder 259/27)
    - Ross, Yuriko (Box-folder 259/28)
    - Ross, Yuriko, others (Box-folder 259/29)
  - Cortege of Eagles
    - Cohan, Cohen, MG, Powell, Randozzo,Winter (Box-folder 244/1)
    - Cohan, MG, Ross, Cohen, Powell (Box-folder 244/2)
    - Cohan, MG, Ross, others (Box-folder 244/3)
    - Cohan, MG, Ross, others (Box-folder 244/4)
    - MG, Powell, others (Box-folder 244/5)
    - MG, Robinson, Ross, Wood, others (Box-folder 244/6)
    - MG, group (Box-folder 244/7)
    - Rooks (Box-folder 244/8)
    - White [George] (Box-folder 244/9)
    - Group (Box-folder 260/1, 266/1)
  - Dancing Ground
    - Asakawa, McGehee, Powell (Box-folder 260/2)
    - Asakawa, McGehee, Powell, others (Box-folder 244/10)
    - Asakawa, Powell (Box-folder 260/4)
    - McGehee, Powell (Box-folder 244/11, 260/4)
    - McGehee, Powell, group (Box-folder 244/12, 260/5)
    - McGehee, group (Box-folder 244/13, 260/6)
    - Group (Box-folder 244/14, 266/2)
    - Women (Box-folder 244/15)
  - Dark Meadow
    - Asakawa (Box-folder 244/16)
    - Asakawa, Walker (Box-folder 244/17)
    - Cohan (Box-folder 244/18)
    - Cohan, Hodes (Linda) (Box-folder 244/19)
    - Hawkins, MG; Hodes (Stuart), others (Box-folder 244/20)
    - Hinkson, Ross; Hinkson, Ross, Wood, Yuriko (Box-folder 244/21, 260/7)
    - Hodes (Stuart), Yuriko, others (Box-folder 244/22)
    - Kimura (Box-folder 244/23)
    - Kimura, Lyman (Box-folder 244/24)
    - Kimura, others (Box-folder 244/25)
    - Lang, Winter, Yuriko (Box-folder 244/26)
    - Lyman (Box-folder 244/27)
    - McLain (Box-folder 244/28)
    - MG, other (Box-folder 244/29)
    - Monte (Box-folder 244/30)
    - O’Donnell (Box-folder 244/31)
    - Sparling (Box-folder 244/32)
    - Turney, MG (Box-folder 244/33)
    - Slides (Box-folder 244/34)
    - Women (Box-folder 244/35)
  - Deaths and Entrances
    - Butler (incl. negative) (Box-folder 260/8)
    - Butler (John and Ethel), Cunningham, Dudley, Fonaroff, Hawkins, Lang, Maslow, MG (Box-folder 245/1)
    - Butler, Cunningham, Dudley, Hawkins, Maslow, MG (Box-folder 245/3)
    - Butler, Cunningham, Hawkins, Horan, MG (Box-folder 245/4)
    - Butler, Cunningham, Horan, Maslow, MG (Box-folder 245/5)
    - Butler, Fonaroff, Lang, MG (Box-folder 245/2)
    - Butler, Hawkins, MG (negative) (Box-folder 260/9)
    - Butler, MG (incl. negative) (Box-folder 260/11)
    - Capucilli (Box-folder 245/6)
    - Capucilli, Garay, Giovanola (Box-folder 245/7)
    - Capucilli, Morin (Box-folder 245/8)
    - Capucilli, Morin, Rooks (Box-folder 245/9)
    - Cohan (Box-folder 245/10)
    - Cohan, Hodes (Stuart) (Box-folder 245/11)
    - Cohen, Hinkson, Ross, Walker (Box-folder 245/12)
    - Cohen, Hinkson, Turney; Cohen, Hinkson, Walker (Box-folder 245/13)
    - Cunningham, Hawkins, MG (Box-folder 245/14)
    - Dudley, Maslow, MG (Box-folder 245/15)
    - Garay, Giovanola (Box-folder 245/16)
    - Gray, Hinkson, Kimura; Gutelius, Hinkson, Kuch, Ross, Turney (Box-folder 245/17)
    - Gutelius, Newton (Box-folder 245/18)
    - Gutelius, Newton, Parkes (Box-folder 245/19)
    - Hawkins (Box-folder 260/12)
    - Hawkins, MG (Box-folder 260/13)
    - Hinkson (Box-folder 245/20)
    - Hinkson, Kuch (Box-folder 245/21)
    - Hodes (Box-folder 245/22)
    - Lang (Box-folder 245/23)
    - MG (Box-folder 245/24, 253/1)
    - MG (Box-folder 260/14-15)
    - Morin, Rooks (Box-folder 245/25)
  - Deep Song
    - MG (Box-folder 245/26)
  - Diversion of Angels
    - Asakawa (Box-folder 245/27)
    - Asakawa, Chao, Delamo, Homsey, Mitchell (Box-folder 245/28)
    - Cohan, Lang (Box-folder 245/29)
    - Cohan, Winter (Box-folder 245/30)
    - Dakin, Terborgh (Box-folder 245/31)
    - Delamo, Kimura, Lyman (Box-folder 245/32)
    - Delamo, Kimura, Tuddy (Box-folder 245/33)
    - Delamo, Kimura, others (Box-folder 245/34)
    - Delamo, Lyman (Box-folder 245/35, 260/16)
    - Eilber (Box-folder 245/36)
    - Eilber, Wengerd (Box-folder 245/37)
    - Hart, Wengerd (Box-folder 245/39)
    - Hinkson, Powell, Winter (Box-folder 245/40)
    - Hinkson, Powell, Winter (incl. negative) (Box-folder 260/17)
    - Hinkson, Ross (Box-folder 245/41)
    - Kimura, Lyman, others (Box-folder 245/42)
    - Lyman; Lyman, other (Box-folder 245/43, 265/2)
    - McGehee (Box-folder 245/44)
    - Ross, others (Box-folder 245/45)
    - Sparling (Box-folder 245/46)
    - Winter, others (Box-folder 260/19)
    - Winter, others (incl. negative) (Box-folder 260/20)
    - Wood (Box-folder 245/47)
    - Contact sheets/proofs (Box-folder 245/48)
    - Group (Box-folder 245/49)
    - Group (incl. negative) (Box-folder 260/21)
    - Unidentified (negative) (Box-folder 245/50)
  - Ecuatorial
    - Delamo, Kimura (Box-folder 245/51)
    - Proofs (Box-folder 245/52)
  - Ekstasis
    - MG (Box-folder 245/53, 261/1)
  - Embattled Garden
    - Hinkson, other (Box-folder 261/2)
    - Kimura (Box-folder 261/3)
    - Kimura, Lyman, Maloney, Parkes (Box-folder 245/54)
    - Kimura, Maloney (Box-folder 245/55)
    - Kimura, Ross (incl. two negatives) (Box-folder 261/4)
    - Kimura, Ross, other (Box-folder 245/56, 261/5)
    - Kimura, others (Box-folder 261/6)
    - [Ross], Turney, other (Box-folder 261/8)
    - Ross, Tetley, Turney, Yuriko (Box-folder 261/7)
    - Ross, other (negative) (Box-folder 261/9)
    - Taylor (Box-folder 245/57)
    - Unidentified (incl. negative) (Box-folder 261/10)
    - Contact sheets/proofs (Box-folder 245/58)
  - Episodes
    - MG (Box-folder 246/1)
    - MG, Ross (Box-folder 246/2)
    - MG, Ross, Wilson [in rehearsal] (Box-folder 246/3)
    - MG, Wilson (Box-folder 246/4)
    - MG, Ross, others (Box-folder 246/5)
    - MG, Wilson, others; MG, group (Box-folder 246/6)
    - MG, other (Box-folder 246/7)
    - Wilson; Wilson, others (Box-folder 246/8)
  - Errand into the Maze
    - Brown, Monte (Box-folder 246/9)
    - Capucilli, White (Larry) (Box-folder 246/10)
    - Dakin (Box-folder 246/11)
    - Kimura (Box-folder 246/12)
    - Kimura, Wengerd (Box-folder 246/13)
    - McGehee, Thompson (Box-folder 246/14)
    - Thompson; Thompson, Turney; Turney (Box-folder 246/15)
    - Set (Box-folder 261/11)
    - Contact sheets/proofs (Box-folder 246/16)
    - Slides/negatives (Box-folder 246/17)
  - Every Soul Is a Circus
    - Asakawa (Box-folder 246/18)
    - Asakawa, others (Box-folder 246/19)
    - Birch, Ross (Box-folder 246/20)
    - Butler, Cunningham, Flier, Marohowsky, Mazia, Hawkins, MG (Box-folder 246/21)
    - Cunningham, Mazia, Flier, Butler, Maslow (Box-folder 253/2)
    - Hawkins, MG (Box-folder 261/12, 265/3)
    - MG (Box-folder 246/22, 261/13)
    - MG (Box-folder 265/4)
    - MG, Cunningham (Box-folder 253/3)
    - MG, Dudley, Hawkins (Box-folder 253/4)
    - Proofs (Box-folder 246/23)
  - Eye of Anguish
    - Cohan, Lang (Box-folder 246/24)
    - Cohan, Ross (Box-folder 246/25)
  - The Flute of Kirshna
    - Sabin, set, various groups and individuals (Box-folder 246/26)
  - Flute of Pan
    - Eilber (Box-folder 246/27)
  - Frescoes
    - Brown (Box-folder 246/28)
    - Brown, Lyman; Lyman, chorus (Box-folder 246/29)
    - Lyman, Wengerd (Box-folder 246/30)
    - Lyman, Wengerd, chorus (Box-folder 246/31)
  - Frontier
    - Lyman (Box-folder 246/32)
    - MG (Box-folder 246/33, 261/14)
    - Winter (Box-folder 246/34, 261/15)
  - Heretic
    - MG, others (Box-folder 246/35)
  - Hérodiade
    - Lang (Box-folder 246/36)
    - MG (Box-folder 246/37, 261/16)
    - MG (Box-folder 261/18)
    - MG (incl. negative) (Box-folder 261/17, 261/19)
    - MG (incl. negatives) (Box-folder 261/20)
    - MG, O’Donnell (Box-folder 246/38)
    - MG, O’Donnell (small size) (Box-folder 246/39)
    - O’Donnell (Box-folder 246/40)
    - Winter (Box-folder 261/21-22)
    - Set (Box-folder 246/41)
  - Imperial Gesture
    - MG (Box-folder 247/1)
  - Judith
    - Asakawa (Box-folder 247/2)
    - Asakawa, White (Box-folder 247/3)
    - Brown [Charles] (Box-folder 261/23)
    - Brown, Foreman, Lyman, Wengerd, White (Box-folder 247/4)
    - Brown [David] (Box-folder 247/5)
    - Capucilli (Box-folder 247/6)
    - Capucilli, White (Box-folder 247/7)
    - Foreman; Foreman, Monte (Box-folder 247/8)
    - Lyman (Box-folder 247/9, 261/24)
    - Lyman, Wengerd (Box-folder 247/10)
    - Lyman, Wengerd, other(s) (Box-folder 247/11)
    - Lyman, others (Box-folder 247/12)
    - MG (Box-folder 247/13)
    - White (Box-folder 247/14)
    - Men (Box-folder 261/25)
    - Set (Box-folder 247/15)
  - Lady of the House of Sleep
    - Louther (Box-folder 247/16)
    - MG, and other(s) (Box-folder 247/17)
    - Group (Box-folder 247/18)
  - Lamentation
    - Eilber (Box-folder 247/19)
    - Lyman (Box-folder 247/20)
    - MG (Box-folder 261/26)
  - Legend of Judith
    - Cohan (Box-folder 247/21)
    - Cain (Box-folder 247/22)
    - Lyman, MG, Ross (Box-folder 261/27)
    - MG (Box-folder 247/23)
    - MG (incl. negative) (Box-folder 261/28)
    - MG, Ross; MG, Ross, other (Box-folder 247/24)
    - MG, Ross, other (incl. negative) (Box-folder 261/30)
    - MG, Thompson, Yuriko (Box-folder 247/25, 261/31)
    - MG, others (Box-folder 247/26, 261/32)
    - Wood (Box-folder 247/27)
    - Set (Box-folder 247/28)
  - Letter to the World
    - Butler, MG (Box-folder 247/29)
    - Cohan (Box-folder 247/30)
    - Cohan, MG (Box-folder 247/31)
    - Dudley, Hawkins, MG (Box-folder 247/32)
    - Dudley, Lang, McGehee, MG, Yuriko (Box-folder 247/33)
    - Dudley, Lang, McGehee, Yuriko (Box-folder 247/34)
    - Dudley, women (Box-folder 247/35)
    - Erdman, MG (Box-folder 247/36)
    - Hawkins, MG (Box-folder 247/37)
    - Lang (Box-folder 247/38)
    - Lang, other (Box-folder 247/39)
    - MG (Box-folder 247/40, 261/33)
    - Contact sheets/proofs (Box-folder 247/41)
  - A Look at Lightning
    - Hodes (Linda), Powell (Box-folder 248/1)
    - Powell, Ross (Box-folder 248/2)
    - [Powell], Ross, Turney (Box-folder 248/3)
    - Powell, Ross, Turney, other (Box-folder 248/4)
  - Lucifer
    - Delamo (Box-folder 248/5)
    - Contact sheets (Box-folder 248/6)
  - Marionette Show
    - Biracree, MacDonald, Sabin (Box-folder 248/7)
  - Mendicants of Evening
    - Group and contact sheets (Box-folder 248/8)
  - Myth of a Voyage
    - Contact sheets (Box-folder 248/9)
  - Night Journey
    - Birch, McGehee, MG, Ross, Turney (Box-folder 248/10, 262/1)
    - Cohan, MG (Box-folder 248/11)
    - Cohan, MG, Ross (Box-folder 248/12)
    - Foreman, Lyman (Box-folder 248/13)
    - Gray (Box-folder 248/14)
    - Gray, Lyman, Wengerd, others (Box-folder 248/15)
    - Gray, Maloney, Wengerd (Box-folder 248/16)
    - Gray, Nureyev (Box-folder 248/17)
    - Gray, Parkes (Box-folder 248/18)
    - Gray, Parkes, Walker (Box-folder 248/19)
    - Gray, Wengerd (Box-folder 248/20)
    - Gutelius (Box-folder 248/21)
    - Hawkins, chorus (Box-folder 248/22, 262/3)
    - Hawkins, Lang, chorus (Box-folder 248/23)
    - Hawkins, MG (Box-folder 248/24)
    - Hawkins, MG, chorus (Box-folder 262/2)
    - Kimura (Box-folder 248/25)
    - Kimura, Walker (Box-folder 248/26)
    - Kimura, Wengerd (Box-folder 248/27)
    - Lang (Box-folder 248/28)
    - Lyman (Box-folder 248/29)
    - Lyman, Wengerd (Box-folder 248/30)
    - McGehee (Box-folder 248/31)
    - MG (Box-folder 248/32, 262/4)
    - MG (Box-folder 265/5, 253/5-6)
    - MG, other (Box-folder 265/7)
    - MG, Ross (Box-folder 248/33, 265/6, 249/14)
    - MG, Ross, chorus (Box-folder 249/15)
    - MG, Ross (incl. negative) (Box-folder 262/5)
    - MG, Ross, chorus (Box-folder 248/34)
    - MG, Ross (Box-folder 249/6)
    - MG, Ross, Taylor (Box-folder 249/7)
    - MG, Taylor; MG, Taylor, chorus (Box-folder 249/8)
    - Nureyev (Box-folder 248/35)
    - Parkes (Box-folder 248/36)
    - Ross (Box-folder 262/6, 249/9)
    - Ross, chorus (Box-folder 249/10)
    - Ross, chorus (negative) (Box-folder 262/7)
    - Ross, Winter (Box-folder 248/37)
    - Ross, Winter, chorus (Box-folder 248/38)
    - Sparling (Box-folder 248/39)
    - Taylor (Box-folder 249/11)
    - Turney (Box-folder 249/1)
    - Wengerd (Box-folder 249/2)
    - Winter (Box-folder 249/3)
    - Chorus (Box-folder 249/4, 265/8)
    - Chorus (Box-folder 249/12)
    - Contact sheets/proofs (small) (Box-folder 249/5)
    - Group (Box-folder 249/13)
  - O Thou Desire Who Art About to Sing
    - Dakin, Terborgh (Box-folder 249/16)
    - Monte (incl. contact sheets) (Box-folder 249/17)
    - Monte, Wengerd (Box-folder 249/18)
  - One More Gaudy Night
    - Set (Box-folder 249/19)
  - The Owl and the Pussycat
    - Brown (Box-folder 249/20)
    - Brown, Monte, Salvatori, White (Box-folder 249/21)
    - Dakin, Kimura, Mitchell, Sparling, Tyers, Wengerd (Box-folder 249/22)
    - Dakin, Mitchell, Tyers (Box-folder 249/23)
    - Eilber (Box-folder 249/24)
    - Eilber, Kimura, Wengerd (Box-folder 249/25)
    - Kimura (Box-folder 249/26)
    - Kimura, Minnelli, Sparling, Terborgh, Wengerd, dolphin chorus (Box-folder 249/27)
    - Kimura, Minnelli, Terborgh, Wengerd (Box-folder 249/28)
    - Kimura, Sparling, Wengerd (Box-folder 249/29)
    - Kimura, Terborgh (Box-folder 249/30)
    - Kimura, Wengerd (Box-folder 249/31)
    - Kimura, Wengerd, White (Box-folder 249/32)
    - MG, Minnelli; Minnelli (Box-folder 249/33)
    - Minnelli, dolphin chorus (Box-folder 249/34)
    - Minnelli, Wengerd (Box-folder 249/35)
    - Monte, Salvatori (Box-folder 249/36)
    - Salvatori (Box-folder 249/37)
    - Sparling (Box-folder 249/38)
    - Stewart (Box-folder 249/39)
    - Wengerd (Box-folder 249/40)
    - White (Box-folder 249/41)
    - Contact sheets (Box-folder 249/42)
  - Part Real-Part Dream
    - Cohan, Hinkson, Ross, Turney (Box-folder 250/1)
    - Cohan, Turney (Box-folder 250/2)
    - Hinkson (Box-folder 250/4)
    - Hinkson, Turney, other (Box-folder 250/5)
    - Ross, Turney (Box-folder 250/6)
    - Turney (Box-folder 250/7)
    - Group (Box-folder 250/8)
    - Set (Box-folder 250/9, 262/8)
    - Women (Box-folder 250/10/)
  - El Penitente
    - Brown, Buglisi, Hochoy (Box-folder 250/11)
    - Gutelius (Box-folder 250/12)
    - Hawkins (Box-folder 250/13, 262/9)
    - McDonald, Wood (David), Wood (Marne) (Box-folder 250/14)
    - MG (Box-folder 250/15)
    - Ross, others (Box-folder 250/16)
    - Contact sheet (Box-folder 250/17)
  - Persephone
    - Group (Box-folder 250/18)
  - Phaedra
    - Cohan, Hodes (Linda), Powell (Box-folder 250/19)
    - Cohan, McGehee, MG, Ross, Winter (Box-folder 250/20)
    - Cohan, MG (Box-folder 250/21)
    - [Cohan], MG (Box-folder 262/10)
    - Cohan, MG (negative) (Box-folder 262/11)
    - Cohan, MG, Winter (Box-folder 250/22)
    - Eilber, Sparling; Eilber, Sparling, Wengerd (Box-folder 250/23)
    - Eilber, Wengerd (Box-folder 250/24)
    - Gain, Hodes (Linda), Powell, other (Box-folder 250/25)
    - Gain, [Powell], Thompson, Winter, Wood, others (incl. negative) (Box-folder 262/12)
    - Hinkson, Hodes, McGehee, MG, Turney (Box-folder 250/26)
    - Hodes (Linda) (Box-folder 250/27)
    - Hodes (Linda), Powell (Box-folder 250/28)
    - Homsey (Box-folder 250/29)
    - Homsey, others (Box-folder 250/30)
    - McGehee, MG, Ross, Winter (Box-folder 250/31, 262/13)
    - McGehee, Ross (Box-folder 250/32, 262/14)
    - MG (Box-folder 250/33)
    - MG (incl. negative) (Box-folder 262/15)
    - MG, Ross (Box-folder 250/34)
    - MG, Winter (Box-folder 250/35)
    - Powell (Box-folder 250/36)
    - Ross, Turney (Box-folder 250/37)
    - Winter (incl. negative) (Box-folder 262/16)
    - Contact sheet (Box-folder 250/38)
    - Unidentified negatives (Box-folder 262/17)
    - Groups (Box-folder 250/39)
  - Phaedra’s Dream
    - Capucilli (Box-folder 250/40)
    - Capucilli, Rooks, White (Box-folder 250/41)
    - Dakin (Box-folder 250/42)
    - Dakin, Morin, White (Box-folder 250/43)
    - Dakin, others (Box-folder 262/18)
    - Morin (Box-folder 250/44)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 262/19)
  - The Plain of Prayer
    - Eilber (Box-folder 250/45)
    - Eilber, Sparling (Box-folder 250/46)
    - Contact sheet/color slides (Box-folder 250/47)
  - Point of Crossing
    - Gray, Wengerd (Box-folder 250/48)
    - Parkes, Smith (Box-folder 250/49)
  - Primitive Mysteries
    - Gutelius, group (Box-folder 251/1)
    - MG (Box-folder 251/2, 262/20)
    - MG (Box-folder 265/9)
    - MG, group (Box-folder 251/3, 265/10)
    - Yuriko (Box-folder 251/4, 262/21)
    - Yuriko, group (Box-folder 251/5, 262/22)
    - Yuriko, group (incl. negative) (Box-folder 262/23-24)
    - Proofs (Box-folder 251/6)
  - Punch and the Judy
    - Cunningham, Hawkins, MG, others (Box-folder 251/7)
    - Hawkins (Box-folder 251/8)
    - Lang (Box-folder 251/9)
  - Rite of Spring
    - Capucilli, White (Box-folder 251/10)
    - Capucilli, White, other (Box-folder 251/11)
    - Dakin (Box-folder 251/12)
    - White, group (Box-folder 251/13)
    - White (Box-folder 251/14)
  - Salem Shore
    - MG (Box-folder 251/15)
  - Sarabande from Transitions
    - MG (Box-folder 253/7)
  - The Scarlet Letter
    - Eilber, Homsey, Nureyev (Box-folder 251/16)
  - Secular Games
    - Eilber, Maloney (Box-folder 251/17)
    - Fisher, MG, Thompson [in rehearsal] (Box-folder 251/18)
    - Fisher, Thompson (Box-folder 251/19)
    - McGehee, Powell (Box-folder 251/20)
    - McGehee, Thompson (Box-folder 251/21)
    - McGehee, Thompson (negative) (Box-folder 251/25)
    - McGehee, others (Box-folder 251/22)
    - Powell, Randazzo, Thompson (Box-folder 251/23)
    - Powell, others; Randazzo, others (Box-folder 251/24)
    - Thompson (Box-folder 251/25, 262/26)
    - Contact sheet (Box-folder 251/26)
    - Group (Box-folder 251/27, 262/27)
  - Seraphic Dialogue
    - Asakawa, Walker (Box-folder 251/28)
    - Dakin (Box-folder 251/29)
    - Dakin, McLain, Tyers, White (Box-folder 251/30)
    - Dakin, Walker, others (Box-folder 251/31)
    - Dakin, White (Box-folder 251/32)
    - Delamo, Eilber (Box-folder 251/33)
    - Delamo, Eilber, McLain, Monte, Tyers; Delamo, McLain, Mitchell, Tyers; Delamo, McLain, Monte, Tyers (Box-folder 251/34)
    - Delamo, Gray (Box-folder 251/35)
    - Delamo, McLain, Tyers (Box-folder 251/36)
    - Eilber (Box-folder 251/37)
    - Eilber, McLain, White (Box-folder 251/38)
    - Eilber, Sparling (Box-folder 251/39)
    - Eilber, White (Box-folder 251/40)
    - Gutelius, Ross, Winter (Box-folder 251/41)
    - Hinkson, Ross, others (Box-folder 251/42)
    - Hinkson, others (Box-folder 251/43)
    - McGehee (Box-folder 251/44)
    - Hodes, McGehee, Winter, Yuriko (incl. negative) (Box-folder 262/28)
    - Hodes, Ross (Box-folder 251/45)
    - Hodes, Ross (negative) (Box-folder 262/29)
    - Homsey (Box-folder 251/46)
    - Homsey, Walker (Box-folder 251/47)
    - Kanda (Box-folder 252/1)
    - Kimura (Box-folder 252/2)
    - Kimura, others (Box-folder 252/3)
    - Lyman (Box-folder 252/4)
    - McGehee (Box-folder 252/5)
    - McGehee, Ross (Box-folder 252/6)
    - McGehee, Ross, Stevens, Turney, other (Box-folder 252/7)
    - McGehee, Ross, Winter, other (Box-folder 252/8)
    - McGehee, Ross, others (Box-folder 252/9)
    - MG, others (Box-folder 252/10)
    - Monte (Box-folder 252/11)
    - Ross (Box-folder 252/12)
    - [Ross] (incl. negative) (Box-folder 262/31)
    - Ross, Turney (Box-folder 252/13)
    - Ross, Turney, others (Box-folder 252/14)
    - Ross, Winter, others (Box-folder 252/15)
    - Ross, others (Box-folder 252/16)
    - Turney (Box-folder 252/17)
    - van der Hoeven (Box-folder 252/18)
    - Walker (Box-folder 252/19)
    - White (Box-folder 252/20)
    - White, other (Box-folder 252/21)
    - Winter (Box-folder 252/22)
    - Winter, others (Box-folder 252/23)
    - Yuriko, others (Box-folder 252/24)
    - Contact sheets/proofs (Box-folder 252/25)
    - Proofs (Box-folder 262/32)
    - Group (Box-folder 252/26)
    - Slides (Box-folder 252/27)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 262/33)
  - Song
    - Barnes, Sparling (Box-folder 252/28)
  - Tangara from Trois Gnossiennes
    - MG (Box-folder 252/29, 262/34)
  - Tangled Night
    - Dakin, Foreman, other (Box-folder 252/30)
  - Temptations of the Moon
    - Capucilli, White, others (Box-folder 262/34)
  - A Time of Snow
    - Lapzseon, MG (Box-folder 252/31)
    - Lapsezon, MG, Ross; Lapsezon, MG, Ross, other (Box-folder 252/32)
    - MG, Ross (Box-folder 252/33)
    - Contact sheet (Box-folder 252/34)
  - Two Primitive Canticles
    - MG (Box-folder 252/35)
  - Voyage/Theatre for a Voyage
    - MG, Ross; Set (Box-folder 252/36)
  - Other Performance Photographs
    - Graham, Georgia (with Denishawn) (Box-folder 265/11-12)
    - Miscellaneous contact sheets (Box-folder 252/37-40)
    - Unidentified performance photographs (Box-folder 265/13, 253/8)
  - Martha Graham Alone
    - Age 2 (Box-folder 254/1)
    - At airport (Box-folder 254/2)
    - Bennington College, 1938 (Box-folder 254/3)
    - Columbia University (in performance), 1935 (Box-folder 254/4)
    - Denishawn (Box-folder 254/5)
    - Denishawn School (Box-folder 263/1)
    - Dogs (Box-folder 254/6)
    - Early roles, (1920s-1930s) (Box-folder 254/7, 263/3)
    - Early roles (Box-folder 263/2)
    - Edinburgh, 1963 (Box-folder 254/8)
    - Greenwich Village Follies, 1924 (Box-folder 254/9)
    - Headshots (Box-folder 254/10, 263/4-6)
    - Madonna (Box-folder 254/11)
    - Outdoors (by tree) (Box-folder 254/12)
    - Painting (Box-folder 254/13)
    - Princess of Isis, 1916 (Box-folder 254/14)
    - Pyramid to Quetzalcóatl, Teotihuacán, Mexico (Box-folder 254/15)
    - Santa Barbara, California (Box-folder 254/16)
    - Sarah Lawrence, 1937 (Box-folder 254/17)
    - Stage shot (Box-folder 254/18, 263/7)
    - Stonehenge, 1967 (Box-folder 254/19)
    - Various roles (Box-folder 254/20)
    - Wearing kimono (Box-folder 254/21)
    - Youth (Box-folder 254/22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 254/23, 263/8-9)
  - Martha Graham with Others
    - Bolshoi Ballet at the Metropolitan Opera, 1966 (Box-folder 263/10)
    - Capucilli, Terborgh at rehearsal for Rite of Spring (Box-folder 254/24)
    - Cohan, Hinkson, Hodes (Linda), McGehee, Ross, Turney, Wood in rehearsal (Box-folder 254/25, 263/11)
    - Cohan, McGehee, MG in rehearsal (Box-folder 263/12)
    - Coolidge, Mrs. Elizabeth Sprague (Box-folder 254/26)
    - Copland, Aaron (Box-folder 254/27)
    - Copland, Nureyev, MG (contact sheet) (Box-folder 254/28)
    - Dance group (Box-folder 254/29)
    - Dance group (1920s) (Box-folder 254/31)
    - DeMille, Agnes (Box-folder 254/32)
    - DeMille, Horst, other (Box-folder 254/33)
    - DeMille; Schuman, William (Box-folder 254/34)
    - Denishawn School dancers (Box-folder 254/35)
    - Denishawn on tour (Box-folder 254/36)
    - Ford, Betty; Ford, Betty with others, 1975 (Box-folder 263/13, 254/45)
    - Ford, Betty and dancers (Box-folder 254/46)